

Contacts



6870 Cedar Rose Crt



(778)-551-8589



Justin.won1214@gmail.com



http://jstn-swm.github.io



<u>jstn-swm</u>



<u>/justin-wang04</u>

ABOUT ME

2nd year Computer Science student specializing in user experience and data structure in back-end development. Motivated to learn and innovate. Active problem solver, exceptional situational awareness to respond to emergency situations.

- Collaborative Leadership
- Strategic Problem Solving
- Organized Execution
- Adaptive Decision Making

Certifications

• Harvard – CS50

Reference

Reference Available upon Request

Languages

English Native Mandarin Native

Justin Wang

Computer Science Student

INTERNSHIP-POSITION

Skills

Web Development JQuery Javascript Node PHP Backend Development C++ Javascript Java Swift

Tools & Industry Knowledge

	$\overline{}$		
Github •		UX	
AWS Network (Self Host)		UI	

Work Experience

Independent

Contractor

Burnaby, BC Jun 2022 - Present

Anne Kang Office Burnaby, BC Jun 2021 - Nov 2023

Sakura Media

Burnaby, BC

Swim Instructor & Volunteer

- Data entry and analysis to accommodate outdated database
- Leadership in optimizing communications with guardians and peers
- Actively devising great facilitation methods and motivation for younger patrons' development
- Generate exceptional visuals for organization's social media traction.
- Personalized assistance for high valued guests in professional environments

Seasonal Sales Associate and Marketing

- Deliver professional service and swift attendance
- Foster strong relationships with patrons through active engagement and product promotion
- Great products sales based on patron suitability and needs

Education

Langara College

Vancouver, BC June 2021 - Present

Burnaby South Secondary

Vancouver BC Graduated - June 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

- Studying Computer Science
- Specializing in Back-End Development
- Data Structures & Algorithms
- Took part in networking projects with Java

High School Diploma

- Graduated with Honours & 2x Principle's List
- Computer Science Club
- Creative Candidate & Designer of Mascot (out of 1700 candidates)
- Film and Editing Projects